Marching to the New Wonderland
The Devil, Justice Spider
We’re delivering the invaluable Energy Seed,
but the kids just can’t keep their guards up.
I have to fix this.
Kids, be careful!
They say that there’s a big, dangerous devil on the Big Tree.
He’s very scary!
A big devil?
It’s working.
It’s the big devil!
Run!
Wait, the “big devil” is real?
Let’s get out of here!
But this is the only road
that’ll take us to the Big Tree’s Summit.
Such a massive spider web.
Spider web?
You don’t mean…
The—
The big devil!
Do you need any help?
Why aren’t you guys eating?
Hurry up.
Don’t let it get cold.
Who are you?
Why do you want to help us?
I’m the Big Tree’s jumping spider.
My name is Justice Spider.
I’m the personification of justice.
Helping others is my favorite thing.
Oh, you’re no “big devil”.
Phew.
The Big Tree World is still dangerous, though.
We can’t let our guard down.
We’ve still got a long way to go.
What should we do?
Don’t worry, I’ll protect you along the way.
Once you’ve eaten, let’s get the ball rolling.
Yay!
Too hot!
Sorry! I added too much pepper.
Stop!
What is it?
Don’t worry,
I’ve got this.
Who did that?
Well, that was close.
Don’t you worry, though.
You’ll be safe with me around.
Thank you, Justice Spider.
Nice move!
It can’t top me or my years of goat-catching experience, though.
You’re not going anywhere.
This road is unsafe!
I’ll find a different path for you.
Wow, that guy is really good at catching goats!
We’d make a great team, I’m sure.
Is everyone alright?
Why do I feel like we always run into trouble
whenever Justice Spider “helps” us?
Yeah.
Is everyone alright?
I’m here to help.
Again?
No!
Hey, stop!
I told you to stop, didn’t I?
I guess Justice Spider is, in fact, the supposed “big devil”.
We can’t keep him around.
Kids,
Justice Spider helped us in good faith.
We shouldn’t go behind his back.
Yes, but…
Chatting in such a dark room will strain your eyes.
I’ll turn on the lights. Where’s the switch?
Hey, that’s my face!
That’s my ear!
There, all nice and bright.
What happened, Mr. Slowy?
I’m… I’m fine.
You guys go on.
Weslie, I agree with your idea.
I collected a list of insects
that need your help.
You should go and give them a hand.
Do they really need me?
Yes, they do.
They’re in the middle of dire crises
and need you more than we do.
Okay, I’ll go right away!
Wait.
Who’s going to protect you guys if I’m gone?
We’ll be just fine. You don’t need to worry.
Goodbye, friends!
Goodbye, Justice Spider!
Oh, they didn’t give me any locations.
Finally, we’ve gotten rid of Justice Spider.
Isn’t this a bit mean of us, though?
Well,
Justice Spider got us into all that trouble.
He’s clumsy, too.
We’ve gotten hurt because of him.
But… he…
Justice—
You guys have hated me all along, huh?
We’re sorry, we just meant that—
I don’t care!
I’ll just go!
Mr. Slowy, what should we do now?
We shouldn’t have done that.
Let’s go apologize to him.
Once I win over Justice Spider,
I can catch all the goats in the world.
Watch this.
Somebody help me!
Could you give me a hand?
Come on up.
Never mind. All I do is cause harm.
I’d better go.
Don’t go!
I’ve been waiting for three days and nights!
I really need your help.
Really?
I believe that you’re the personification of justice.
The personification of justice?
Okay, I’ll help.
All done.
With all of the wood scraps, no one will fall in again.
Let me out first, would you?
See? All I do is bring trouble.
What do you mean?
Look at your just face,
and your set of just skills.
Most importantly, you have a heart of justice.
Your words are sincere.
You must be a good guy.
People always say that.
However,
that one group of goats are always harassing me!
Goats?
I’d wholeheartedly helped them deliver things.
Not only did they not thank me,
they dumped me in the pit, too.
Look, my finger’s hurt.
Those are their true colors, huh?
No wonder they hated the just me!
Would you help me capture those goats, then?
Of course I will! Let’s go.
Mr. Slowy, we couldn’t find Justice Spider.
We must apologize to him face to face once we do.
You evil goats! Put your hands behind your back!
Justice Spider?
We’re sorry. We want to apologize.
Don’t fall for it.
They love playing the victim.
Wolffy?
Oh, really?
You’re all done for!
Onto the trains, now!
Don’t let them get away!
They blocked the road with acorns.
Watch this.
The road is all clear.
Throw them elsewhere, would you?
Sorry, I forgot.
The goats have gotten away.
Actually, I set up a giant web up ahead.
They have nowhere to run.
Warning: Threat detected.
I hear the goats screaming.
They must have hit it.
Is everyone alright?
Yes.
It seems that Wolffy has convinced Justice Spider.
Let’s just get out of here.
Make sure they can’t catch up to us.
Did I hear Wolffy and Justice Spider screaming just now?
I’ll be back!
END